<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sip on My technology blog</title>
    <link>https://hhgarland.me/tags/sip/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sip on My technology blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:34:59 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hhgarland.me/tags/sip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CUBE Reconfiguration</title>
      <link>https://hhgarland.me/posts/2024-01-04-cube-reconfiguration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:34:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hhgarland.me/posts/2024-01-04-cube-reconfiguration/</guid>
      
      <description>I was inspired to simplify my CUBE configuration after reading this article on the Cisco Learning website. The voice service voip section of the configuration was already in pretty good shape; however, the folliwing areas needed some work:
SIP URI definitions E.164 pattern maps Dial peer groups Server groups Translation profiles Dial peers Defining the SIP URIs For the inbound WAN and LAN dial peers, I wanted to match on the incoming uri via headers.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using SIP Profiles on Cisco VoIP Gateways</title>
      <link>https://hhgarland.me/posts/2023-07-21-sip-profiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 18:15:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hhgarland.me/posts/2023-07-21-sip-profiles/</guid>
      
      <description>The problem I stumbled upon an issue with outbound calls failing that were being made from a Sangoma analog gateway with FreePBX being used as a SIP proxy between the endpoint and the PSTN gateway.
The call flow looks like this:
1. Sangoma Analog Gateway &amp;lt;-----&amp;gt; 2. FreePBX &amp;lt;-----&amp;gt; 3. Cisco Gateway &amp;lt;-----&amp;gt; 4. PSTN Issue with the SIP INVITE Upon further inspection I found that the initial INVITE was being rejected by the carrier:</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Failed type 6 encryption on password&#39;</title>
      <link>https://hhgarland.me/posts/2023-06-16-failed-type-6-encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 06:44:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hhgarland.me/posts/2023-06-16-failed-type-6-encryption/</guid>
      
      <description>I ran into an issue recently when attempting to change the password on an previously configured SIP binding (information has been changed for security reasons):
site-1-cube(config-sip-ua)#credentials username 3334445555 password 0 J2[%)_Ie realm nyc.provider.com Failed type 6 encryption on password I had never seen the error Failed type 6 encryption on password before and I struggled somewhat in understanding how to change this. I ran into this article and it was subsequently the same solution I was given by Cisco TAC:</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
